nationalfuelgas.com 2019-03-28

# Privacy Policy

Welcome to the web site of National Fuel Gas Company and its affiliated and subsidiary companies (“National Fuel ”). National Fuel respects the privacy of individuals who use our website. This Web Privacy Policy (the “Policy ”) explains our online information practices and is designed to assist you in making informed decisions while using our website. Please read the Policy carefully and in its entirety.

## The Information We Collect And How We Use It

National Fuel automatically receives and records the following information from visitors to our site: IP addresses; domain names; user names; date, time and length of visits; and browser types. This data is gathered to evaluate and improve our website.

Additionally, National Fuel makes use of the Google Analytics service to track aspects of our visitors' personal information, including demographic information and web browsing activity, which may include sources of referral that direct visitors to our site and usage metrics relative to such visits. For more information on the types of data tracked through Google Analytics and how this data might be used, [click here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners). If you wish to opt out of sharing data through Google Analytics, you may follow the instructions noted [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

## Collection of personal information

You may choose to provide personal information such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, bank account information or other similar information on this or other National Fuel websites. If you choose not to provide requested personal information this may result in reduced website functionality. National Fuel’s usage of this information will be consistent with this Policy.

## How National Fuel Uses Personal Information

National Fuel may use voluntarily provided personal information for the following purposes:

  * Respond to visitor requests, inquiries and applications;
  * Create, administer and communicate with you about your account (including any purchases and payments);
  * Provide investor services;
  * Evaluate your interest in employment and contact you regarding possible employment; 
  * Operate, evaluate and improve our business (including development of services through statistical reports; analyzing our products, services and website; administering our websites; and performing accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation and collection activities);
  * Protect against and prevent fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims and other liabilities, and manage risk exposure and quality; and
  * Conduct investigations and comply with applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our Policy.

## Use of Website Cookies and Similar Technologies:

Like most companies, National Fuel uses cookies and similar technologies (“cookies ”) on our websites to facilitate and improve your online experience.

## How we use cookies

Cookies contain small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit our website. Cookies are sent back to our website to allow us to recognize your device. Recognizing your device with cookies allows our site to help you navigate efficiently to obtain the information and services you requested.

In some cases Advertising Cookies may be used to inform you of available services or programs that might be of interest to you.

## Unless you disable the cookies on our website, by using the website you agree to our use of those cookies.

Most browsers allow you to manage cookie preferences. If you decide to disable cookies on our site, you may reduce the website functionality and may not be able to take advantage of all website features.

## Third Party Links and Sharing tools

To enhance our website functionality and your experience, National Fuel may include links and sharing tools to other (third party) sites. These third party sites may also place and access cookies on your device. National Fuel does not control the placement or access of these third party cookies. National Fuel is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of linked third party sites. You should check the relevant third party website(s) for more information about these cookies and whether and how you may make choices about them.

## Confidentiality and Security

National Fuel limits access to your personal information to:

  * Employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information.
  * Third party service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. Such third parties are contractually restricted from using or disclosing the personal information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements.

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including through bankruptcy).

## Legally Required Disclosures

In addition to the access listed above, National Fuel may be required, by applicable law, subpoena, court order, or other legal process to disclose your personal information, and it is our policy to comply with any such requirements.

## How We Protect Your Information

National Fuel utilizes industry appropriate practices to protect the data transmitted or received via our website from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, or alteration. Such practices include using Transport Layer Security (TLS) encryption technology and secure HTTPS posts during data transmission. Please note, given the nature of the internet, National Fuel cannot absolutely guarantee the confidentiality of any personal information that you provide via our website or promise that the information you provide will never be obtained by unauthorized persons.

## Children

Our website is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and National Fuel will not knowingly collect information from children under the age of thirteen.

## Access, Correct and Update Personal Information

You may obtain a copy of the personal information that you have provided to National Fuel through your use of our website and you may correct, change or remove any personal information by contacting us via the following link https://www.nationalfuelgas.com/email.aspx.

If you request that the personal information that you provided to National Fuel be removed from National Fuel's records, please be aware that you may not be able to continue to use National Fuel's online services, which may require the collection of such information.

To protect your privacy, National Fuel will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before correcting, changing, removing, or forwarding personal information to you.

## Modifications to Our Policy

National Fuel reserves the right to modify or update this Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Policy, we will make every effort to promptly post the revised Policy on our website. You should visit our website periodically to review the current Policy. Use of our website after the posting of a revised Policy constitutes your agreement with the revised policy.

## Acceptance of this Policy

By using our website, you signify your acceptance of this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, your sole remedy is not to use this website. Your continued use of this website following the posting of changes to this Policy will be deemed to be your acceptance of those changes.

## Additional Questions

Please click here to contact us if you have any additional questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy.
